{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Water Feature Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/40442/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40442,"taskName":"Water Feature - Install a Fountain or Waterfall","taskDescription":"Install a Fountain and/or a Waterfall","xmTaskDescriptor":"Water Feature Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":262,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Water pond features Waterfall Feature","textMessagingName":"Fount/Waterfall","rolloverLongDesc":"Typically found outdoors \u0026 integrated into the landscaping, some water features can be built indoors to provide decoration, humidity \u0026 soothing sounds. Construction usually entails creating a pool, adding attractive surrounding features such as rock gardens, installing plumbing, adding accent lighting, hooking up a pump \u0026 perhaps adding plants \u0026 small fish. See separate categories for larger ponds requiring a dams.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes fountains, waterfalls, goldfish ponds.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install a Fountain and/or a Waterfall.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Water Fountain Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install Waterfall","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":33,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Fountain or Waterfall Water Feature","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Water Feature - Install a Fountain or Waterfall","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Water Feature Project","urlName":"Water-Feature-Install-a-Fountain-or-Waterfall","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Water Fountain \u0026 Waterfall Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Water,pond,features,Waterfall,Feature,Fountain","emcCategoryOid":-12034,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":733,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40442/":{"taskOID":40442,"originalTaskOID":40442,"setID":733,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4230,"questionDisplayText":"Waterfall Feature","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of waterfall feature do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4026,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Natural freeform waterfall","answerDisplayText":"Natural freeform waterfall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2592,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Formal precast fountain","answerDisplayText":"Formal precast fountain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4231,"questionDisplayText":"Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where do you want to add a waterfall or fountain?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":924,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Back yard","answerDisplayText":"Back yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5675,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Side yard","answerDisplayText":"Side yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2661,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Front yard","answerDisplayText":"Front yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3211,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Indoors","answerDisplayText":"Indoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4232,"questionDisplayText":"Reason for Waterfall/Fountain","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you want a waterfall or fountain?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2560,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Focal point in new landscape","answerDisplayText":"Focal point in new landscape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":684,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Addition to existing landscape","answerDisplayText":"Addition to existing landscape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1397,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Circulate water in existing pool or spa","answerDisplayText":"Circulate water in existing pool or spa","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1396,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Circulate water in existing pond","answerDisplayText":"Circulate water in existing pond","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4230,"questionDisplayText":"Waterfall Feature","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of waterfall feature do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4026,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Natural freeform waterfall","answerDisplayText":"Natural freeform waterfall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2592,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Formal precast fountain","answerDisplayText":"Formal precast fountain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4026,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Natural freeform waterfall","answerDisplayText":"Natural freeform waterfall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2592,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Formal precast fountain","answerDisplayText":"Formal precast fountain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4231,"questionDisplayText":"Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where do you want to add a waterfall or fountain?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":924,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Back yard","answerDisplayText":"Back yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5675,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Side yard","answerDisplayText":"Side yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2661,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Front yard","answerDisplayText":"Front yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3211,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Indoors","answerDisplayText":"Indoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":924,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Back yard","answerDisplayText":"Back yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5675,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Side yard","answerDisplayText":"Side yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2661,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Front yard","answerDisplayText":"Front yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3211,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Indoors","answerDisplayText":"Indoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4232,"questionDisplayText":"Reason for Waterfall/Fountain","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you want a waterfall or fountain?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2560,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Focal point in new landscape","answerDisplayText":"Focal point in new landscape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":684,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Addition to existing landscape","answerDisplayText":"Addition to existing landscape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1397,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Circulate water in existing pool or spa","answerDisplayText":"Circulate water in existing pool or spa","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1396,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Circulate water in existing pond","answerDisplayText":"Circulate water in existing pond","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2560,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Focal point in new landscape","answerDisplayText":"Focal point in new landscape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":684,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Addition to existing landscape","answerDisplayText":"Addition to existing landscape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1397,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Circulate water in existing pool or spa","answerDisplayText":"Circulate water in existing pool or spa","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1396,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Circulate water in existing pond","answerDisplayText":"Circulate water in existing pond","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}